to access your Microsoft Office programs
you would need to go down at the Start
menu which involve left-hand corner if
you click on the windows icon that will
bring up a list of programs that are
installed on your computer everything is
installed alphabetically so as you
scroll down you will see the programs
that have been installed such as Excel
PowerPoint and Word which are the three
programs that you will use during this
course to access the program you would
simply click on the word icon and then
that would open up Microsoft Word to
make it easier to access your software
without having to go through the storm
and you you can't right click on that
and then select a more option and pin to
taskbar this will then place the icon on
your taskbar so by clicking on that that
will open the program directly without
having to go through the Start menu you
can then do this for your PowerPoint and
your Excel which will just speed things
up a little bit if I click on the icon
now that will launch word and take me to
the good morning welcome screen